Chef Leonardo has a decimal integer N and a non-zero decimal digit dd. N does not contain the digit zero; specifically, N should always be treated as a decimal integer without leading zeroes.

Chef likes dd and does not like any other digit, so he decided to change N. He may apply the following operation any number of times (including zero): append the digit dd to the decimal representation of N (dd becomes the least significant digit of N), then remove one occurrence of one digit from the decimal representation of N.

Chef has already changed a lot of numbers and he got bored. Now, he wants to know the smallest possible value of N which can be obtained by performing the operation described above. Can you help him?

Input
The first line of the input contains a single integer T denoting the number of test cases. The description of T test cases follows.
The first and only line of each test case contains two space-separated integers N and dd.
Output
For each test case, print a single line containing one integer - the minimum number Chef can obtain.

Constraints
1≤T≤1,0001≤T≤1,000
1≤N≤10181≤N≤1018
N does not contain the digit 00
1≤d≤91≤d≤9
Subtasks
Subtask #1 (40 points):

1≤T≤1001≤T≤100
1≤N≤1091≤N≤109
Subtask #2 (60 points): original constraints

Example Input
3
35 4
42 4
24 9
Example Output
34
24
24
Explanation
Example case 1: Chef can remove the digit 55 and add 44 to the end of N. Then, N becomes 3434.

Example case 2: Chef can remove the digit 44 from the begiNing of N, add 44 to the end of N and get N=24N=24.

Example case 3: Chef caNot make his number any smaller.