Chef and Dhyey have become friends recently. Chef wants to test Dhyey's intelligence by giving him a puzzle to solve.

The puzzle contains an integer sequence A1,A2,…,ANA1,A2,…,AN. The answer to the puzzle is the maximum of Ai%AjAi%Aj, taken over all valid ii, jj.

Help Dhyey solve this puzzle.

Input
The first line of each test case contains a single integer N.
The second line contains NN space-separated integers A1,A2,…,AN
Output
For each test case, print a single line containing one integer — the answer to the puzzle.

Constraints
2≤N≤1052≤N≤105
1≤Ai≤1091≤Ai≤109 for each valid ii
Subtasks
Subtask #1 (30 points): 2≤N≤1,0002≤N≤1,000
Subtask #2 (70 points): 2≤N≤1052≤N≤105
Example Input 1
5  
1 2 3 4 5  
Example Output 1
4  
Example Input 2
6  
5 5 5 2 3 8
Example Output 2
5